nh7.in 2016-06-08

# Privacy Policy > NH7 | Discover new music from India and around the world

Here at NH7, we respect your privacy and are committed to keeping any personal information you share with us secure and out of the hands of any African princes/genitalia enlargement product providers/creepy dudes who want to “make fraanship” with you/equivalent. We, like some of you, spend almost all of our time on the interwebs and we hate it when our personal information is shared with people who we don’t want it shared with (this doesn’t stop us sharing intimate details of our personal lives on Twitter or Facebook or YouTube comment flame wars, but still). So in the interest of full disclosure, here’s our privacy policy.

The information we collect from you for the sake of registration (which you knowingly and willingly provide us) on NH7.in, or NH7 Festivapp or NH7 inTown, will not be shared with any third party. The only people we may share it with is government authorities (and only in the instance when we are required to do so by law) in case some crazy shit goes down and they need our user database for a terrorist crackdown or to see how much porn you’ve been downloading (JK on that last one, though if the government could find out how much porn you’ve been downloading just from your email address, then at least we would’ve established that someone in the government knows how to use the internet).

We also send out a few emailers, which you can unsubscribe to if you find them annoying (we try our best to make them as interesting as possible, fo realz) by hitting the ‘Unsubscribe’ button at the end of those emails.

That’s basically it. If you need any clarifications or have any issues with our privacy policy, drop us an email at [kvlt@nh7.in](mailto:kvlt@nh7.in)

And now, some statuatory warnings:

_Don’t email and drive. Champions use the internet responsibly. Social media and driving may be injurious to health. Resist the urge to tweet what you had for breakfast. Be cool, we’re on your side._
